MOJTABA NAMAZI FARD

Frontend Developer

Dob: 1998
Tehran, Iran

**** 09210886520

in <u>mojtaba-namazy</u>

<u>mojtaba-namazy</u>

anfnamazi

Summary

Hi I'm a software engineer with 4+ years of experience in front-end development, current tech stack is: TypeScript, React.

Worked in 3 software companies on different project stages: requirements analysis, UI and product design, choosing tech stack, architecture design, and software development.

Skills

- ✓ Javascript
- Typescript
- React.js
- ✓ Redux / MobX
- ✓ Next.js

✓ Webpack

Cypress

- ES6+
- Babel
- ✓ Leaflet.js
- ✓ Cesium.js

- ✓ Design pattern
- ✓ OOP✓ Material-UI
- Rest-API
 HTML
- ✓ Graph-QL✓ CSS
- ✓ Git✓ SASS

Experience

Frontend Developer | March 2019 - Present

SHARIF HAMRAH PAZHOOHAN

- Implemented performance optimization strategies for adding large amounts of data to the leaflet map container.
- Utilized Cesium's APIs to integrate geospatial data layers and create dynamic visualizations for geospatial applications.
- Optimized performance of 3D rendering and interactions for smooth user experience across various devices.
- Participated in the planning and execution of sprints, ensuring timely delivery of high-quality code.
- Conducted code reviews to maintain code quality and adherence to coding standards.

Frontend Developer | December 2020 - December 2021

HIMART (Mihan Industrial Group)

- Leveraged Webpack's `TreeShakingPlugin` to eliminate unused code within modules, resulting in a 20% reduction in bundle size and a 15% improvement in initial load time.
- Implemented dynamic imports and React's `Suspense` component to lazily load feature-specific code, enabling users to interact with core functionalities quickly while non-essential features download in the background.
- Implemented strategies for filtering and sorting shops in near area.

Frontend Developer | September 2021 - December 2021

DADE KAVAN | ANDISHE BARTAR

• Successfully led the redesign of food ordering process resulting improve user engagement.

Education

Bachelor of Science: **Software Engineering** | 2016 - 2020

Sadra University, Tehran